https://www.weeklypostnc.com/privacy-policy/

Hometown
ECHO Training Offers Firearms Training For All Ages And Skill Levels
Hometown
2020 Summer Mint Hill Arts Show Winners
Hometown
Local Second-Grader Supports Levine Children’s NICU through Art
Hometown
News You Can Use: What’s Happening at the Local Library?
Hometown
James B. Crump VFW Post 2423 Honors Sgt. Michael Verardo with…
Sports
Sports
CMS Follows NCHSAA Guidelines – Fall Sports and Scholarships in Play
Hometown
Pine Lake Golfer Gets Eleventh Career Hole In One
Press Release
NCHSAA Response to Governor Roy Cooper’s Announcement on a Return to…
Sports
NCHSAA Spotlights Four Athletes With 2020 Tony Simeon Courage Awards
Sports
NCHSAA Cancels June Scholastic Basketball Recruiting Events
Columns
AllBiz 2 Biz AdvertisingContractor CornerDG MartinEdward JonesFamily Fun Around TownHappily Ever After DivorceHealthy Headlines from Novant HealthJohn HoodLeisure Time TravelLet’s Get Moving with AnnaLife in TouchLive, Laugh and LoveMint Hill Animal Hospital Pet TipsParent PagePatrick EssSandy’s Scoop on PhotographySimply EntertainingSweet Harvest HappeningsThe Recipe BoxTips from Tag’m Kennel
Leisure Time Travel
Domestic Travel By Personal Transportation
Let’s Get Moving with Anna
How To Prioritize Need vs. Nice To Have In Your House…
Healthy Headlines from Novant Health
How To Keep Kids Safe As Playgrounds Open To Larger Crowds
Parent Page
Pumpkin Decorating Ideas For Kids
The Weekly Post Privacy Policy
Last Updated on May 25, 2018.
This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of information about you in connection with your use of our services, including those offered through our websites, emails, and mobile applications (collectively, the “Service”). The terms “we”, “us”, and “The Weekly Post” refer to The Weekly Post Inc., an Limited Liability Corporation with its headquarters in Mint Hill, NC. When you use the Service, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.
1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT
We may collect and store information about you in connection with your use of the Service, including any information you transmit to or through the Service. We use that information to provide the Service’s functionality, fulfill your requests, improve the Service’s quality, engage in research and analysis relating to the Service, personalize your experience, track usage of the Service, provide feedback to third party businesses that are listed on the Service, display relevant advertising, market the Service, provide customer support, message you, back up our systems, allow for disaster recovery, enhance the security of the Service, and comply with legal obligations. Even when we do not retain such information, it still must be transmitted to our servers initially and stored long enough to process.
Please also note:
Account Information: If you create a The Weekly Post account, we may store and use the information you provide during that process, such as your full name, email address, zip code, physical address, and other information you may provide with your account, such as your gender, phone number, and birth date. We may publicly display your first name and last initial, as well as any photo or other content you submit through the registration process, as part of your account profile. You can modify some of the information associated with your account through your account settings. If you believe that someone has created an unauthorized account depicting you or your likeness, you can request its removal by flagging it.
Communications: When you sign up for an account or use certain features, you are opting to receive messages from other users, businesses, and The Weekly Post. You can manage some of your messaging preferences through your account settings, but note that you cannot opt out of receiving certain administrative, transactional, or legal messages from The Weekly Post. For example, if you make a reservation, order food, place yourself on a waitlist, or request a quote from a business through the Service, we may send you messages about your transaction using the contact information you provide, including through automated SMS text messages to your phone number. We may also track your actions in response to the messages you receive from us or through the Service, such as whether you deleted, opened, or forwarded such messages. If you exchange messages with others through the Service, we may store them in order to process and deliver them, allow you to manage them, and we may review and disclose them in connection with investigations related to use of the Service, as well as our efforts to improve the Service. We may not deliver messages that we believe are objectionable, such as spam messages, fraudulent solicitations, or requests to exchange reviews for compensation. If you send or receive messages through the Service via SMS text message, we may log phone numbers, phone carriers, and the date and time that the messages were processed. Carriers may charge recipients for texts that they receive. We may also store information that you provide through communications to us, including from phone calls, letters, emails and other electronic messages, or in person. If you are a representative of a business listed on The Weekly Post, we may contact you, including by phone or email, using the contact information you provide us, make publicly available, or that we have on record for your business. Our calls with you may be monitored and recorded for quality purposes.
Transactions: If you initiate a transaction through the Service, such as a reservation or purchase, we may collect and store information about you, such as your name, phone number, address, email, and payment information (such as a credit card number and expiration date), as well as any other information you provide to us, in order to process your transaction, send communications about them to you, and populate forms for future transactions. This information may be shared with third parties, and third parties may share such information with us, for the same purposes. When you submit credit card numbers, we encrypt that information using industry standard technology. If you write reviews about businesses with which you transact through the Service, we may publicly display the fact that you transacted with those businesses. For example, if you make a dinner reservation through the Service and write a review about your experience, we may publicly display the fact that you made your dinner reservation through the Service.
Activity: We may store information about your use of the Service, such as your search activity, the pages you view, the date and time of your visit, businesses you call using our mobile applications, and reservations and purchases you make through the Service. We also may store information that your computer or mobile device may provide to us in connection with your use of the Service, such as your browser type, type of computer or mobile device, browser language, IP address, WiFi information such as SSID, mobile carrier, phone number, unique device identifier, advertising identifier, location (including geolocation, beacon based location, and GPS location), and requested and referring URLs. We may also receive and store your location whenever our mobile applications are running, including when running in the background, if you enable our mobile apps to access such information in the course of using the Service. You may be able to limit or disallow our use of certain location data through your device or browser settings, for example by adjusting the “Location Services” settings for our applications in iOS privacy settings.
Different Devices: You may access the Service through different devices (e.g., your mobile phone or desktop computer) and different platforms (e.g., the The Weekly Post website or The Weekly Post mobile app). The information that we collect and store through those different uses may be cross-referenced and combined, and your contributions through one The Weekly Post platform will typically be similarly visible and accessible through all other The Weekly Post platforms.
2. COOKIES
We, and third parties with whom we partner, may use cookies, web beacons, tags, scripts, local shared objects such as HTML5 and Flash (sometimes called “flash cookies”), advertising identifiers (including mobile identifiers such as Apple’s IDFA or Google’s Advertising ID) and similar technology (“Cookies”) in connection with your use of the Service, third party websites, and mobile applications. Cookies may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Service, such as your browser type, search preferences, IP address, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. Cookies may be persistent or stored only during an individual session.
The purposes for which we use Cookies in the Service include:
Purpose Explanation
Processes Intended to make the Service work in the way you expect. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us whether you have already signed up for an account. Authentication, Security, and Compliance intended to prevent fraud, protect your data from unauthorized parties, and comply with legal requirements. For example, we use Cookies to determine if you are logged in. Preferences Intended to remember information about how you prefer the Service to behave and look. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us whether you have declined to allow us to send push notifications to your phone.Notifications Intended to allow or prevent notices of information or options that we think could improve your use of the Service. For example, we use a Cookie that stops us from showing you the signup notification if you have already seen it. Advertising Intended to make advertising more relevant to users and more valuable to advertisers. For example, we may use Cookies to serve you interest-based ads, such as ads that are displayed to you based on your visits to other websites, or to tell us if you have recently clicked on an ad. Analytics intended to help us understand how visitors use the Service. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us how our search suggestions correlate to your interactions with the search page.You can set some Cookie preferences through your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect the functionality of the Service. The method for disabling Cookies may vary by device and browser, but can usually be found in your device or browser preferences or security settings.
3. THIRD PARTIES
Third parties may receive information about you as follows:
Advertisers: We may allow third parties to use Cookies through the Service to collect the same type of information for the same purposes as we do. In doing so, we adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. Third parties may be able to associate the information they collect with other information they have about you from other sources. We do not necessarily have access to or control over the Cookies they use, but you may be able to opt out of some of their practices by visiting the following links: Network Advertising Initiative, Omniture, Digital Advertising Alliance and PrivacyChoice. Please note that opting out does not prevent the display of all advertisements to you. Additionally, we may share non-personally identifiable information from or about you with third parties, such as location data, advertising identifiers, or a cryptographic hash of a common account identifier (such as an email address) to facilitate the display of targeted advertising. You may be able to limit our sharing of some of this information through your mobile device settings, as described in Section 2 above, or through the Service’s settings.
Content Partners: We allow third party partners to use and display some of the public content available through the Service, such as your photos, reviews, and other information detailed in Section 1(b) above.
Service Providers: We may rely on third party providers to support or provide some of the services that are available through the Service, such as reservations and food delivery. We may also rely on third party providers to perform certain services for us in connection with your use of the Service, such as communications and hosting services, network security, technical and customer support, tracking and reporting functions, quality assurance testing, payment processing, our own marketing of the Service, and other functions. We may share information from or about you with these third party providers so that they can perform their services or complete your requests. These third party providers may share information with us that they obtain from or about you in connection with providing their services or completing your requests. Third party providers may also share this information with their subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control. Some of our web pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to you from our third party providers, while preserving the look and feel of the Service. In such cases, please note that the information you provide is being provided to the third party.
Aggregate or Anonymous Information: We may share user information in the aggregate with third parties, such as businesses that are listed on The Weekly Post and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertisements. We may also disclose anonymized information about your use on The Weekly Post, for example if you engage in a transaction in connection with The Weekly Post, we may publicly disclose information about the transaction without providing identifying information about you or otherwise disclosing your participation in the transaction.
Business Transfers: We may share information from or about you with our parent companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires The Weekly Post, or all or substantially all of our assets, that company will possess the same information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Businesses on The Weekly Post: We may share information from or about you (such as your age and gender), your devices, and your use of the Service (such as which businesses you bookmark or call) with businesses listed on The Weekly Post. You may adjust your account settings to increase or decrease the amount of information we share. Keep in mind that businesses may still see your public activity and posts, and may receive information from or about you when you transact or communicate with them, through The Weekly Post or otherwise, regardless of your settings (see Section 1 above). Additionally, if you make a phone call to a business through or in connection with your use of the Service, we may share information about your call with the business that the business would have received had you called them directly, such as the date and time of your call and your phone number. You may be able to limit our ability to collect and share your phone number through your phone’s settings or phone service provider.
Investigations and Legal Disclosures: We may investigate and disclose information from or about you if we have a good faith belief that such investigation or disclosure: (a) is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process or law enforcement requests served on us; (b) is helpful to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service; or (c) protects our rights, reputation, property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public, such as disclosures in connection with The Weekly Post’s Consumer Alerts program. If you flag or otherwise complain to us about content through the Service, we may share the substance of your complaint with the contributor of that content in order to provide an opportunity for the contributor to respond.
Links: The Service may link to third party services, like a business’s URL. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with them, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on or applicable to all such third party services.
Third Party Accounts: If you sign up for, or log into, The Weekly Post using a third party service like Facebook or Google, or link your The Weekly Post account to your account with a third party service like Facebook or Twitter, we may receive information about you from such third party service. If you post content to a third party service through the Service, that third party service will also receive that content, which will be visible to anyone that has access to it through that third party service.
4. CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL DATA
Other users may be able to identify you, or associate you with your account, if you include personal information in the content you post publicly. You can reduce the risk of being personally identified by using the Service pseudonymously, though doing so could detract from the credibility of your contributions to the Service. The Weekly Post users can also use the Find Friends feature to find one another based on their names or email addresses. You can adjust the settings for this feature in your account settings. Please also note that the messages you send or receive using the Service are only private to the extent that both you and the person you are communicating with keep them private. For example, if you send a message to another user, that user may choose to publicly post it. Also, we may access and disclose such messages in the course of investigations relating to use of the Service.
5. DATA RETENTION AND ACCOUNT TERMINATION
We may retain information about you for the purposes authorized under this Privacy Policy unless prohibited by law. For example, we may retain information to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service or to comply with legal obligations. Please note that businesses cannot remove their business listings, ratings, or reviews by closing their accounts.
6. CHILDREN
The Service is intended for general audiences and is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us here. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account.
7. SECURITY
We use various safeguards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
8. CONTACT
You may contact us online concerning our Privacy Policy, or write to us at the following address:
The Weekly Post
7427 Matthews-Mint Hill Rd.
Suite 105-184
Mint Hill, NC 28227
9. MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will govern our collection, use, and disclosure of information about you and will be located here. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email or by posting a notice on the Service prior to the effective date of the changes. By continuing to access or use the Service after those changes become effective, you acknowledge the revised Privacy Policy.
10. CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS: YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
We do not disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose of directly marketing their goods or services to you unless you first agree to such disclosure. If you have any questions regarding this policy, or would like to change your preferences, you may contact us at the address listed above in Section 8.
Featured articles
News You Can Use: Medical Professionals Weigh In On The Flu Shot
Happenings Mary Beth Foster -
October 6, 2020
CHARLOTTE - What is the flu shot, and why do I need it?
“The flu vaccine causes antibodies to develop in the body about two...
ECHO Training Offers Firearms Training For All Ages And Skill Levels
Hometown Mary Beth Foster -
September 25, 2020
CHARLOTTE - ECHO Training, owned and operated by Michael Pegram, offers a wide variety of firearms training and safety classes for all ages and...
2020 Summer Mint Hill Arts Show Winners
Hometown Brodie Lowe -
September 16, 2020
MINT HILL, NC - Mint Hill Arts recently held their Annual Summer Novant Art Show.  Sponsored by Novant Health (Mint Hill Medical Center), the...
Local Second-Grader Supports Levine Children’s NICU through Art
Hometown Mary Beth Foster -
September 7, 2020
MINT HILL, NC - Three years ago, Vanessa Birch, mom to then-five-year-old Hazel, was confronted with a problem familiar to all parents of preschoolers:...
Fall Splendor – Raleigh’s Juniper Level Botanic Garden opens two Weekends in September
Happenings Staff Writer -
September 4, 2020
RALEIGH, NORTH CAROLINA – Juniper Level Botanic Garden, a $7.5 million gift to North Carolina State University, will open two weekends in September for...
ABOUT USThe Weekly Post is a locally owned, family operated newspaper serving Locust, Oakboro, Midland, Stanfield & Red Cross NC. Since 1974, The Weekly Post has been serving readers and advertisers. Contact us: contact@weeklypostnc.comFOLLOW US
Terms of service
Contact us
© Copyright 2018 The Weekly Post
We understand: ads are not what you are here for. But advertising helps fund our journalism and keep the lights on. So, please add us to your ad blocker whitelist to continue enjoying The Weekly Post.
Refresh Now
